<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<!--
  ~ Catroid: An on-device visual programming system for Android devices
  ~ Copyright (C) 2010-2017 The Catrobat Team
  ~ (<http://developer.catrobat.org/credits>)
  ~
  ~ This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU Affero General Public License as
  ~ published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the
  ~ License, or (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ An additional term exception under section 7 of the GNU Affero
  ~ General Public License, version 3, is available at
  ~ http://developer.catrobat.org/license_additional_term
  ~
  ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the
  ~ GNU Affero General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU Affero General Public License
  ~ along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Create@School</string>

    <string name="dialog_restricted_login_policy_text">To offer you all collaborative benefits of our services and the associated account, it is necessary to collect certain data from you.\n\n

    &#8226; Your Create@School account is not associated to any personal data within the scope of the application provider (Catrobat).
        Furthermore, no such data gets collected through the provided services (as not explicitly stated otherwise).\n\n

    &#8226; To avoid misuse of our services (e.g., through user contributed uploads or comments) for illegal purposes,
        the user generated public data will be stored internally in a database, together with a timestamp and the used IP address.\n\n

    &#8226; To improve our services (apps and websites) and to do scientific research on ICT and STEM education,
        we use Google Analytics, Crashlytics and Firebase by Google Inc. to get metadata about the usage (e.g., timestamps, visited pages/screens, used operating system, and information about the network provider).
        This analysis and the collected data is not linked to your profile and does not contain any personal information.\n\n

    &#8226; All Services are provided by the non-profit free open source Catrobat project under the umbrella of the International Catrobat Association – Verein zur Förderung freier Software (Graz, Austria).\n\n

    &#8226; To get in touch with us, please send an E-Mail to contact@catrobat.org or mail us to Catrobat,\n
        c/o\n
        Institute of Software Technology,\n
        Inffeldgasse 16b/II,\n
        8010 Graz, Austria.\n\n
    </string>
</resources>
